Hello, I'm Park Jin-beom, who is working on visual creative in the name of TAGIREN.
Recently, I worked on a girl group aespa's We Flash album i-aespa character artwork.
Hi, I'm Yon Sanchez, a digital fashion creator and 3D artist.
My work focuses on creating realistic and visual-friendly clothes.
I worked with Jin-beom on the We Flash Universe project.
Two years ago, while preparing for an online lecture,
I wanted to explain to the students how to make clothes and how to use existing asset clothes.
At that time, I was looking for assets to use.
At that time, Yon had a lot of professionally and systematically produced clothes,
so based on Yon's clothes,
I wanted to explain how to customize them to the students.
That's when I got in touch with Yon.
I think that's when we became friends.
I looked at Jin-beom's Instagram and thought,
Okay, this person knows what she's doing.
I love her style.
I want to work with her.
I-aespa's character artwork was uploaded to my SNS on SM Entertainment.
I saw the previous character artwork and thankfully, he contacted me about the artwork.
I think it was really good at the time.
I always pursued a style that gave me a good opportunity to redesign the character of I-aespa
and design new clothes, so I had a lot of fun working on it.
I think it was a meaningful project.
At that time, I was in touch with Yon, and I know Yon's excellent skills,
so I asked him to work with me on the I-aespa costume production project.
Jin-beom sent me a direct message asking me about this collaboration,
and without thinking much about it, I said,
Let's go ahead with this.
We connected very quickly. It was very natural.
It can't be any better than this.
Collaborating together has been very fluid.
We actively share connections, we give each other mutual feedback, and we help each other a lot.
The project had a clear line from the beginning.
The process was very fluid.
I quickly made the basic structure and then added the details.
Yon and I had worked on a collaboration several times before,
and thanks to this project, we were able to quickly proceed with the project with smooth communication.
Thanks to the collaboration between Clou and Marvelous Designer,
I think we were able to work faster and more easily.
Especially using Marvelous Designer,
we had more time to work on concepts and level of detail,
so we were able to create a high-quality artwork.
We were also able to work more effectively and efficiently
because we collaborated and communicated using Clou and Marvelous Designer.
And since the files are compatible, it's much easier to review them.
I have been working with other K-pop artists since IESPA's Reflash Universe project.
I want to have a career in the game industry as well as fashion or entertainment,
but my ultimate goal is to become a 3D artist in various industries, especially as a 3D character artist.
I loved working on the IESPA project.
It opened many doors for me to different projects,
with fashion brands, the automotive industry, and projects where you can always learn something new.
As a dream, I would like to create my own fashion brand.
But it's a long-term dream, so I'm not in a hurry to do it.
I need to keep learning, exploring, meeting people, and keeping myself informed about trends.
What is the most important part of your work?
Clou is an essential part of my work.
I would say it's my daily life.
Thanks to this, I can experiment digitally with different forms.
I'm looking forward to showing you my new projects.
Right now, I'm mainly dealing with Marvelous Designer,
and I know that the compatibility between Clou and Marvelous Designer software
is really good.
Also, in order to achieve my goal,
Marvelous Designer is a tool that should not be absent,
so I plan to use it consistently for my career.
What is your goal?
To be continued in the next episode.